<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ND Handbell China Tour Blog</title>
    <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ND Handbell China Tour Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Choir</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/about/</guid>
      <description>For more information about the Notre Dame Handbell Choir, check out our website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell to China</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/final-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/final-day/</guid>
      <description>Our final day in China!
We started the day with an adventure to the Wide and Narrow Alleys, where we did a ton of shopping and acquired a ridiculous amount of souvenirs. We were joined by Sichuan University students as our guides, and without them we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have made it to lunch!
In the afternoon, we headed over to Ping’an Qiao Church, where we played for their 4 pm mass in English, attended by international students and residents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandas!</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/pandas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/pandas/</guid>
      <description>Today we saw pandas!
Giant and red pandas both were at the breeding center in Chengdu. We took a massive amount of pictures and had the chance to see pandas under a year old. A few of us sent postcards with pandas on them to family members to commemorate this fun morning.
The afternoon consisted of setup for our second and final concert at Sichuan University. It was an amazing show with solos from Sichuan students and Joe Tang on piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chengdu and Sichuan University</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/sichuan-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/sichuan-university/</guid>
      <description>We began our adventure tour of Sichuan University, even seeing a gigantic bell on their campus!
We then took a speeding tour through part of their museum, focusing on Chinese folk art. We saw clothing from traditional wedding ceremonies, carvings and beautiful paper, and shadow puppets made out of leather.
We then met with the Vice President for Internationalization for Sichuan University, to discuss our mural goals of international collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Cathedral Concert and Sightseeing</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/south-cathedral/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/south-cathedral/</guid>
      <description>Today was the perfect blend of sightseeing, performances, and faith.
We started our day adventuring to Tian&amp;rsquo;anmen Square and the Forbidden City. We saw ancient buildings, got a history lesson, and took some amazing pictures.
Next we headed to a Catholic Church in Beijing, the South Cathedral. It serves 10,000 parishioners! We learned about the history of the Catholic Church in China, and that it began over 400 years ago in the place we were standing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting the Great Wall</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/great-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/great-wall/</guid>
      <description>We climbed the Great Wall of China!
We spent the full day, our day &amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; from ringing a formal concert, on the Great Wall of China. It was an amazing, once in a lifetime experience (for most of us). We climbed many, many stairs up to stand on the actual wall.
And then we got to ring bells there. We packed them in backpacks surrounded by sweatshirts and socks, and all bells (and people) arrived safely when we got to the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BGG Liturgy and PKU Concert</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/pku-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/pku-concert/</guid>
      <description>Today can be broken down into two bell performances: one at a Liturgy and one at a concert. This is pretty standard for our bell choir.
If you add another detail, today becomes so very unique and impossibly amazing.
Our liturgy was not in the Basilica of the Sacred Heart, but on the 17th floor of Genesis Beijing, home of Notre Dame&amp;rsquo;s Beijing Global Gateway! We had a view of Beijing as we rang pieces we had played in the Basilica only last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1: Photos</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/day-1-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/day-1-photos/</guid>
      <description>All packed up and ready to go!    The choir poses in front of a loaded bus    Checking in at the airport    Waiting in the terminal    Group photo in front of our plane    In our seats getting ready for takeoff    A view from the plane    Safely on the ground in Beijing     Checking in to the hotel    Sitting down to eat our first meal in China    A sampling of the food    Brett: &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handbell Article in The Observer</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/observer-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/observer-article/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Notre Dame, Hello Beijing</title>
      <link>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/goodbye-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdf730.github.io/chinablog/posts/goodbye-hello/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s nearly 3 in the morning. CoMo 328, home of the handbell choir, is strewn with packing material, handbell cases, tablecloths, foam, and binders. The cases are labeled &amp;ldquo;Fragile&amp;rdquo; in English and Chinese. The binders are stuffed with a wide variety of music. In a few short hours, the sun will come up and the choir will gather from across campus to empty the contents of the cluttered room onto a bus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>